[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carol"]}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What do you say then to America as you say, it makes me feel safe?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "then", "to", "America", "as", "you", "say", ",", "it", "makes", "me", "feel", "safe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I think Carol had it exactly right when we interrupted what she said.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Carol", "had", "it", "exactly", "right", "when", "we", "interrupted", "what", "she", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Alan Dershowitz?", "question_tokens": ["Alan", "Dershowitz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "What you do about it, Alan Dershowitz?", "question_tokens": ["What", "you", "do", "about", "it", ",", "Alan", "Dershowitz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, first of all, the picture should have been published.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "the", "picture", "should", "have", "been", "published", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Carol Roth?", "question_tokens": ["Carol", "Roth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "All right.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carol Roth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "CC", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Alan?", "question_tokens": ["Alan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Think about some of the greatest and most iconic photographs ever published.", "answer_tokens": ["Think", "about", "some", "of", "the", "greatest", "and", "most", "iconic", "photographs", "ever", "published", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What benefit did this photo have?", "question_tokens": ["What", "benefit", "did", "this", "photo", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "And to mark history.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "to", "mark", "history", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "What does this photo have any -- have any benefit for?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "this", "photo", "have", "any", "--", "have", "any", "benefit", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "DT", ":", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Well, this is the very debate that I'm sure is being had all over America because they had been used, as I say, by almost every other form of media now who are therefore repeating the apparent offense of running the original picture which is hypocritical if you take a view against it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "this", "is", "the", "very", "debate", "that", "I", "'m", "sure", "is", "being", "had", "all", "over", "America", "because", "they", "had", "been", "used", ",", "as", "I", "say", ",", "by", "almost", "every", "other", "form", "of", "media", "now", "who", "are", "therefore", "repeating", "the", "apparent", "offense", "of", "running", "the", "original", "picture", "which", "is", "hypocritical", "if", "you", "take", "a", "view", "against", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Why can't they get around the table and negotiate properly?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "they", "get", "around", "the", "table", "and", "negotiate", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Because all people care about is getting elected.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "all", "people", "care", "about", "is", "getting", "elected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Well, what do you make of this and what does he make of this?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "and", "what", "does", "he", "make", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I think the morale is set so low right now on both sides.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "morale", "is", "set", "so", "low", "right", "now", "on", "both", "sides", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "And that is a very bad position for the Republicans to find themselves in, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "is", "a", "very", "bad", "position", "for", "the", "Republicans", "to", "find", "themselves", "in", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "And the polls support that.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "the", "polls", "support", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Is that an option?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "an", "option", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "I'm just --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "My granddaughter?", "question_tokens": ["My", "granddaughter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yes, just hold on, ma'am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "just", "hold", "on", ",", "ma'am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, have you ever heard anything so ludicrous?", "question_tokens": ["Alan", "Dershowitz", ",", "have", "you", "ever", "heard", "anything", "so", "ludicrous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "It's the worst imitation I've ever heard.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "worst", "imitation", "I", "'ve", "ever", "heard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Abby, final word on this?", "question_tokens": ["Abby", ",", "final", "word", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I think it's pretty innocent and gave us all a laugh today so --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "pretty", "innocent", "and", "gave", "us", "all", "a", "laugh", "today", "so", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Is it actually news in the sense that this is the first we've heard of this or are the Pentagon do you think now briefing this is a reality?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "actually", "news", "in", "the", "sense", "that", "this", "is", "the", "first", "we", "'ve", "heard", "of", "this", "or", "are", "the", "Pentagon", "do", "you", "think", "now", "briefing", "this", "is", "a", "reality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, there have been reports already that Syria has weaponized its sarin, it's a nerve gas, already into Scud missiles, into artillery, and in the bombs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "have", "been", "reports", "already", "that", "Syria", "has", "weaponized", "its", "sarin", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "nerve", "gas", ",", "already", "into", "Scud", "missiles", ",", "into", "artillery", ",", "and", "in", "the", "bombs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Pentagon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "How do we know this intelligence is true?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "know", "this", "intelligence", "is", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Well, I suppose we don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "suppose", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "And what did he say?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "he", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "He said, no, not yet.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "said", ",", "no", ",", "not", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "The question is, twofold, one is Assad likely to do this as one last hurrah, and secondly, what will America actually do if it comes to it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "question", "is", ",", "twofold", ",", "one", "is", "Assad", "likely", "to", "do", "this", "as", "one", "last", "hurrah", ",", "and", "secondly", ",", "what", "will", "America", "actually", "do", "if", "it", "comes", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBN", ",", "CD", "VBZ", "NNP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "First of all, I just don't think that we're being duped by the administration.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "just", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "we", "'re", "being", "duped", "by", "the", "administration", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last hurrah"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Why would he risk the wrath of the world descending on him over such an action?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "he", "risk", "the", "wrath", "of", "the", "world", "descending", "on", "him", "over", "such", "an", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "It's hard to see how it is possibly advances his cause except as part of a negotiation.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "see", "how", "it", "is", "possibly", "advances", "his", "cause", "except", "as", "part", "of", "a", "negotiation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "When do the colonels come after him to use a Latin phrase?", "question_tokens": ["When", "do", "the", "colonels", "come", "after", "him", "to", "use", "a", "Latin", "phrase", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I don't think that happens.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "happens", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Did he need to do this and what is the fallout going to be here?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "need", "to", "do", "this", "and", "what", "is", "the", "fallout", "going", "to", "be", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "How are you feeling about it now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "feeling", "about", "it", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "That's the tragedy.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "tragedy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "What should America be doing that it's not, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "America", "be", "doing", "that", "it", "'s", "not", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Well, I think -- you know, I think that Hillary Clinton has made a very, very strong statement today.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "think", "that", "Hillary", "Clinton", "has", "made", "a", "very", ",", "very", "strong", "statement", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "It's just absolutely disgusting, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "absolutely", "disgusting", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "No, it certainly is.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "certainly", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Is he getting more than me?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "getting", "more", "than", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "We'll have to check that out.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ll", "have", "to", "check", "that", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Is she nice, Taylor Swift?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "she", "nice", ",", "Taylor", "Swift", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "So fantastic.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "fantastic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Taylor Swift"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "When we talk about these Christmas presents, which obviously there are a lot made in China, in India and other places, that flood into America and to Europe, what responsibility do businesses have that sell these products to try and find out what is going on at the origin or them, in terms of these sweat shops with these young kids?", "question_tokens": ["When", "we", "talk", "about", "these", "Christmas", "presents", ",", "which", "obviously", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "made", "in", "China", ",", "in", "India", "and", "other", "places", ",", "that", "flood", "into", "America", "and", "to", "Europe", ",", "what", "responsibility", "do", "businesses", "have", "that", "sell", "these", "products", "to", "try", "and", "find", "out", "what", "is", "going", "on", "at", "the", "origin", "or", "them", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "these", "sweat", "shops", "with", "these", "young", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "RP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, good businesses will be checking the supply chain.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "good", "businesses", "will", "be", "checking", "the", "supply", "chain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Christmas"], "LOCATION": ["China", "India", "America", "Europe"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["India"]}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "MD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "And what pressure should countries, perhaps like America, be putting on countries like India to be dealing with this child labor issue?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "pressure", "should", "countries", ",", "perhaps", "like", "America", ",", "be", "putting", "on", "countries", "like", "India", "to", "be", "dealing", "with", "this", "child", "labor", "issue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "MD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "India at the moment has no law that bans child labor completely.", "answer_tokens": ["India", "at", "the", "moment", "has", "no", "law", "that", "bans", "child", "labor", "completely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "India"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Malala"]}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What can we do about the treatment of young people like her that are being victimized by the Taliban, by other organizations like that, to try to protect them going forward?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "we", "do", "about", "the", "treatment", "of", "young", "people", "like", "her", "that", "are", "being", "victimized", "by", "the", "Taliban", ",", "by", "other", "organizations", "like", "that", ",", "to", "try", "to", "protect", "them", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "You've got remember, Malala was shot simply because she wanted to go to school.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "remember", ",", "Malala", "was", "shot", "simply", "because", "she", "wanted", "to", "go", "to", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121205pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "What do you think should be happening here to try and get a deal to avoid the fiscal cliff happening?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "should", "be", "happening", "here", "to", "try", "and", "get", "a", "deal", "to", "avoid", "the", "fiscal", "cliff", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "I have no doubt that people are working very hard to get a deal.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "doubt", "that", "people", "are", "working", "very", "hard", "to", "get", "a", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]